<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


<string name="accept">Accept</string>
<string name="eula_string">COPYRIGHTS:

\nCopyright 2017 Auricle. All Rights Reserved.

\n\nTERMS and CONDITIONS:

\n\nLICENSED APPLICATION END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT

\n\nThe Products transacted through the Service are licensed, not sold, to You for use only under
    the terms of this license, unless a Product is accompanied by a separate license agreement, in which
    case the terms of that separate agreement will govern, subject to Your prior acceptance of that
    separate license agreement. The licensor ("Application Provider") reserves all rights not expressly
    granted to You. The Project that is subject to this license is referred to in this license as the
    "Licensed Application." If user is found in violation of Terms and Conditions provided by Auricle
    and its services, then Auricle and its affiliate partners and third parties have permission from user
    to remove user\'s account(s) and delete user\'s content that was created through Auricle and its Services.

\n\nINTELLECTUAL PROPERTY

\n\nYou agree that Auricle, including but not limited to Auricle projects, graphics, user interface,
    audio clips, editorial content, and the scripts and software used to implement Auricle, contains
    proprietary information and material that is owned by Auricle and/or its licensor(s), and is protected
    by applicable intellectual property and other laws, including but not limited to copyright. You
    agree that you will not use such proprietary information or materials in any way whatsoever except
    for use of Auricle in compliance with this Agreement. No portion of Auricle may be reproduced in
    any form or by any means, except as expressly permitted in these terms. You agree not to modify,
    rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, or create derivative works based on Auricle in any manner,
    and you shall not exploit Auricle in any unauthorized way whatsoever, including, but not limited
    to, by trespass or burdening network capacity.

\n\nYOUR CONTENT
\n\nOwnership: You retain all rights and ownership in your content. Auricle does not claim any ownership
    rights in your content.

    License to Your Content: Even though we do not claim ownership of your content, we do need certain
    licenses to your content in order to operate and enable the Services. We need your permission to do
    things. Our Services also provide you features that may require our systems to access, store, and
    scan Your Stuff. You give us permission to do those things, and this permission extends to our
    affiliates and trusted third parties we work with.


\n\nThis license agreement shall be governed by the laws of The United States of America, Kansas and
shall inure to the benefit of Auricle or its assigns.

\n\nDISCLAIMER / LIMITATION OF LIABILITY:
\n\nBuyer acknowledges that the software may not be free from defects and may not satisfy all of buyer\'s
needs. Auricle warrants all media on which the software is distributed for 60 days to be free from defects
in normal use. The software and any accompanying written materials are licensed \"AS IS\". Buyer\'s exclusive
remedy during the warranty period (if any) shall consist of replacement of distribution media if determined to be
faulty. In no event will Auricle be liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damage or
damages resulting from loss of use, or loss of anticipated profits resulting from any defect in the software,
even if it has been advised of the possibility of such damage. Some laws do not allow exclusion or limitation
of implied warranties or liabilities for incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitations or
exclusion may not apply. Recordings made through Auricle Services cannot be used in court litigation in small, local,
federal courts for civil suits, civil lawsuits, local or federal lawsuits, and local or federal
settlements. Auricle and its affiliate partners and third parties are not held liable for any ongoing and/or
foreseeable court actions, litigation, testimonies, and damages pertaining to but not limited to civil lawsuits,
settlements, and other forms of litigation. Auricle is not held liable if user records and/or edits content
without the permission(s) of other parties within the recording pertaining to and not limited to states that require
all party-consent or one-party consent.

\n\nPRIVACY POLICY:
\n\nThis policy ensures that user\'s recordings are protected when fundamentally first created. However,
    Auricle is not held liable if You, as the user, take recording and publish it in a public forum that the user
    did not receive permissions from other parties that were recorded in audio clips and used for user\'s self-interest(s).
    Per DISCLAIMER mentioned above, Auricle is not held liable for any damages.

\n\nSPECIFIC RESTRICTIONS:
\n\nIn accordance with the COMPUTER SOFTWARE RENTAL ACT OF 1990, this software may not be rented, lent or leased.
\n\nThe software and accompanying documentation may not be provided by a \"Backup Service\" or any other vendor
which does not provide an original package as composed of Auricle, including but not limited to all original
distribution media, documentation, registration cards, and insertions.

\n\nBy clicking on I Agree, I hereby:

\n\nAgree and consent to the User Agreement, its policies, and the Privacy Policy.
    Expressly instruct Auricle to communicate specific information about me and my account to third
    parties in accordance with the Privacy Policy.</string>
</resources>